newmatilda.com 2004-12-05

# New Matilda

**New Matilda Website Privacy Statement**

New Matilda Pty Ltd (NM) is subject to National Privacy Principles, the Privacy Act 1988 the Information Privacy Act 2000 (Commonwealth) and various State Legislation as well as other applicable laws and codes effecting your personal information. NM staff are trained to respect your privacy in accordance with the standards required under the Act and NM is committed to protecting your privacy. The following sets out how NM will deal with personal information recorded through the use by you of its web sites.

**1\. Collecting your Information  
Information Automatically Logged**

NM may make a record of your visit and log any of the information for the purposes of  
\- statistical and business purposes  
\- providing you with relevant product and service (including assessing your personal information and identifying you)  
\- managing and administering the product or service to be provided to you.

The information which may be collected may include your, name, postal or email address, date of birth, financial details, tax file number, date and time of visit, pages accessed, documents downloaded, the previous site visited and the type of browser used and any other information NM considers necessary. If you are not a newsletter subscriber, or a NM staff member and you send us a message, NM will record your e-mail address.

**User Registration**  
If personal information is collected during your visit via a web site and held by NM, every effort will be made to ensure that the information which NM stores in different ways including paper and electronic form is secure. NM will take all reasonable steps to protect it from misuse and loss and unauthorised access, modification or disclosure. Some of the ways we do this are:  
1\. By way of confidentiality requirements for our employees,  
2\. Document storage security policies  
3\. Security measures for systems access;  
4\. Only allowing access to personal information where the person seeking access has satisfied the identification requirements for access.

**External Links**  
As some NM sites contain links to other sites. NM is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites and the user should familiarise themselves with the privacy policies attaching to those websites and NM disclaims any responsibility and/or liability in respect of information and its use on those sites.

You will need to contact or review those websites directly to ascertain their privacy standards policies and procedures.

**2\. Use of Personal Information**  
Personal information you supply on-line will be used by NM and its staff in conducting the business of NM and in providing you with the services and products available from our website. Such uses shall include product planning and development, provision of services and products, maintaining reviewing and developing NMs business systems, procedures and infrastructure in providing managing or administering our product, or service being provided to you, planning and development including research and surveys and statistical analysis as required or authorised by law and be when you have given your consent.

**3\. Disclosure of Personal Information**  
NM will not disclose personal information concerning you to parties outside NM. However, registered users may receive anonymous e-mail messages from other registered users. Actual email addresses will not be made available or published on NM web sites for general use.

**4\. Data Quality/Access**  
NM will always try to maintain accurate, complete and up-to-date information regarding users. If you think that your personal information retained by NM requires changing or removal please contact NM as appropriate.
